<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Storyland</string>
    <string name="Subtitle">Are you ready to embark on a magical journey and discover endless stories in Storyland?</string>

    <!--    Story1-->
    <string-array name="scenes_story1">
        <item>All Easter Bunnies go to the Easter Bunny School, to learn the three most important things...</item>
        <item>One, Painting Easter eggs: nice and bright.</item>
        <item>Two, Hiding Easter eggs: not too hard, and not too easy.</item>
        <item>Three, and very important: reading maps.</item>
        <item>Some children live in faraway places, some in hard-to-find places...</item>
        <item>Our Easter Bunny is very new, and he must got a BIG BIG PARK... to hide eggs for the children playing in the park</item>
        <item>"This map of this park isn\'t so easy, Water?" He asks a frog sitting by the pool, \"Is the BIG BIG sandpit nearby?\". Frog lauphs. "Just follow the path and ask butterflies"</item>
        <item>Easter Bunny hops off, following the path. "Oh! The butterflies in the flower garden!"</item>
        <item>Easter Bunny stops, and the butterflies fly around his head. "Is the BIG BIG sandpit nearby" he asks.</item>
        <item>The butterflies all laugh. "Follow the path and ask the BIG fish in the water." And they flutter back into their flowers. Easter Bunny hops off, following the path.</item>
        <item>"Oh a BIG fish!, Is the BIG sandpit nearby?" he asks.   The big fish in the water laughs. "Follow the path to the climbing playgrund. It isn\'t far".</item>
        <item>Easter bunny stops at the climbing playground and some children shout from high up. "Hello Easter Bunny, can we help you?"</item>
        <item>Easter Bunny looks up at the climbing frame. "Is the BIG BIG sandpit nearby", he asks.</item>
        <item>"Follow the path, it isn\'t far. And hurry up! we are waiting for you to hide the Easter eggs. You\'re late!". Easter Bunny hops off, following the path.</item>
        <item>He looks up and he sees the BIG BIG sandpit at last, and the park keeper looking down at him.</item>
        <item>"You\'re late. The children will be here soon, so you\'d better be quick hiding those eggs"</item>
        <item>Easter Bunny starts to hide the bright coloured Easter eggs. The park keeper looks down at the map that Easter Bunny show him.</item>
        <item>"But you are holding it upside down!" the Park keeper laughs, very loud.</item>
        <item>"Oooops!" Easter Bunny looks at the map. "I\'m a new Easter Bunny, but i\'m learning fast! i\'ll be better next Easter!</item>
    </string-array>

        <!--    story2-->
    <string-array name="scenes_story2">
        <item>Nobody ever talks about me. I don\'t know why, because i\'m the most important bear in the story. I am grandma Growl, and i\'m the best porridge maker in the world.</item>
        <item>Papa Growl likes to keep us fit, and he loves long walks. Bears like to walk, we never run. I get out of those long walks by stying at home and making oh-so-special porridge. </item>
        <item>We all love porridge. Papa Growl\'s porridge salty. Mama Growl has her porridge with crunchy brown sugar. Little Growl is just like me: he loves honey\'s porridge.</item>
        <item>I wave my walker bears off early. So nice to have quiet time after i have stirred the porridge. I have a big yellow armchair in my kitchen, perfect to snooze.</item>
        <item>I didn\'t hear that little Goldie girl sneak in, and i certainly didn\'t hear her eat little Gorgie\'s porridge. But i heard that CRASH-BANG! when she broke his chair. </item>
        <item>"Well, who are you?", i looked straight at Miss Goldie, "Oh sorry, i didn\'t see you, sorry about the chair, the leg fell of". "I am Goldie Locks, we live just outside the woods..."</item>
        <item>"No wonder the leg fell off, did you eat little Gorgie\'s porridge?", "Sorry, i was hungry, well the honey porridge is just perfect".</item>
        <item>Upstairs, Goldie bounced around on the beds, eventough i asked her not to. "At least take off you shoes, please." I growled a kindly growl.</item>
        <item>"I\'d better get those muddy shoes cleaned. I\'ll let little Miss Goldie have a nap". Cleaning muddy shoes is best done outside with a good hard brush.</item>
        <item>Papa Growl noticed the porridge problem straight away. Well, Goldie had left the spoon in the browl.</item>
        <item>Mama Growl noticed the chairs. "Who has been messing up our chairs?" And little Georgie was really miffed that his chair was broken.</item>
        <item>Papa Growl was bounding up the stairs, four at a time. Before i could explain, Goldie Locks opened her eyes wide and screamed. She jumped out.</item>
        <item>We all shouted "Don\'t jump out of that window, little girl...", "Ouch, we tried to tell you", Georgie looked up, "I SAID I'D FIX THAT CHAIR!".</item>
        <item>We all growled again. It was meant "hope you're not hurt" growl. But maybe it sounded like a bear growl. Goldie looked up, and run as fast then never came back for her nice clean shoes.</item>
        <item>When Goldie got home, with no shoes, her mother was not pleased. Goldie tried hard to explain...</item>
        <item>Even worse, she had to wear her big sister\'s old shoes. She tried to tell them about the bears and porridge, but they wouldn\'t listen.</item>
        <item>Little Georgie\'s favorite goodnight storry is about the little girl who jumped of the window. Georgie\'s looks up at the bedroom shelf at the clean Goldie shoes.</item>
        <item>Of course, by the time i get to the last bit...Little Georgie Growl is always fast asleep.</item>
        <item>Georgie would love to see Goldie again, and wants to give her shoes back to her. "Goldie you shoes are at our house clean!".</item>
        <item>So if YOU happen to find one of those little stickers, you aren\'t far from our house! Come and visit!.</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--    story3-->
    <string-array name="scenes_story3">
        <item>We arw going on a trip. I ask mama what to pack. She says, "The things that really matter".</item>
        <item>We stop at the windmill for breakfast. the jungle gym is so much fun. </item>
        <item>I forget my toy. I\'m sad in the car but Tando is happy. "Hooray! Now you can play with me!", he says.</item>
        <item>We stop at a farm to see some animals. Tando is searching so hard for a springbok.</item>
        <item>A monkey gets away with his headphones.</item>
        <item>He is sad in the car. "Hooray! Now you can sing with me!", I say.</item>
        <item>We stop at a roaring waterfall. We are so excited, we are pushing and pulling.</item>
        <item>Papa falls in the water, and so does his map.</item>
        <item>He is sad in the car, but mama is happy. "Hooray! Now i can help you find our way!", she says.</item>
        <item>We stop at the roadside vendor to buy some mielies.</item>
        <item>Mama bends over to pick the best ones, and her glasses fall and break.</item>
        <item>Mama is sad in the car, but papa is happy. "Hooray! Now we can find our way together!", papa says.</item>
        <item>We stop on an ancient hill to get a view of the valley. Papa is making silly jokes for us to smile for the picture.</item>
        <item>but...</item>
        <item>When we get back to the car, it won\'t start. Everyone stops laughing. "Don't worry..."says Mama. "We can still have a good time. We are the things that really matter".</item>
        <item>And so, we do have a good time. By playing and singing and finding our way together, while enjoying the best mielies.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--    story4-->
    <string-array name="scenes_story4">
        <item>"Hurry, Thabo. Mama is making lunch". Calls Tumi.</item>
        <item>Where are you going, Thabo?</item>
        <item>I\'m comiiiiiing...</item>
        <item>His friends don\'t understand why he chooses lunch over their game, but Thabo has a secret.</item>
        <item>Mama\'s lunches are special.</item>
        <item>On Monday, mama shapes their food like little bugs wriggle and crwal, making Tumi shriek in fright. "EEEEE!". But they are yummy fruit and vegetable, and not very scary at all.</item>
        <item>On Tuesday, she makes a lio that roars so loudly the house shakes. "ROAR!". But, it\'s just delicious pasta and cheese.</item>
        <item>On Wednesday, mama creates a chicken that wakes up the whole street. "CLUCK CLUCK PAKAA!". But it\'s just a plate of juicy fruit.</item>
        <item>On Thursday, she builds a noisy truck. Thabo and Tumi cover their ears. "VROOOM!". But, it\'s just a sweet strawberry jam sandwich.</item>
        <item>On friday, mama makes a beautiful garden filled with flowers, birds and ladybugs. "TWEET TWEET!". But, it\'s healthy pap, beans and a crunchy salad.</item>
        <item>"Mama, what\'s for lunch?", asks Tumi. "Yes, mama", says Thabo. "What are you making today?"</item>
        <item>Thabo and Tumi can\'t wait another second. Their tummies are grumbling. Finally, mama is ready. "What is it mama?", asks Thabo, lickingh is lips.</item>
        <item>It\'s Thabo, Tumi and mama!. "Mmm, our favourite, your famous stew and rice.". "Thank you, mama!".</item>
        <item>What will mama make on Sunday?</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--    story5-->
    <string-array name="scenes_story5">
        <item>Frog loved looking at the stars. He wanted to jump up and touch them.</item>
        <item>He climbed a big rock, and reached out for them. But they were out of his reach. The stars were SO far away!</item>
        <item>Then, he saw a hillock. Up he climbed. He stretched his hands, but the stars were still out of reach.</item>
        <item>Frog saw a coconut tree nearby. It was very tall. "Ah", he tought. "This will work now".</item>
        <item>He started to climb the tree. He climbed with great difficulty.</item>
        <item>He stretched his hands... but the stars were still out of his reach.</item>
        <item>He was disappointed. He looked down. His heart skipped a beat in fear.</item>
        <item>He put a hand to his heart and told himself, "I won\'t be scared. I can do it!"</item>
        <item>Then he saw a pond. The stars were twinkling in the water.</item>
        <item>He gazed at the stars and was joyous. He dived into the pond.</item>
        <item>The closer he got the pond, the closer he seemed to the stars.</item>
        <item>SPLASH!. He hit the surface of the water.</item>
        <item>He climbed out and sat on the blank.</item>
        <item>He sat and watched the stars twinkling in the pond.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>